[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "What's it been like for you since that dreadful incident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "It's very hard, but we get up every morning, through people's prayers, their support, the people that love us, our friends and our family, and people all across the world, who send us their prayers, that allows us to get up every single morning and do what we have to do to go to school and go to work and just one step at a time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Are they too young, really, to understand what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "River is too young to understand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April 21st"], "PERSON": ["Wyatt"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "How did you find out that he'd been killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Actually, Wyatt was scheduled to come home the morning of April 21st.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "I mean do you have to live with the risk every day when you're married to somebody that does this kind of job, or do you kind of think it's never going to happen to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "He never actually said something directly to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jason"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "That there was a problem, that there was a clear danger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "That would be Jason.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Why was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Well, to my knowledge, it was deemed the well from hell because there was so many problems on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transocean"], "LOCATION": ["New Orleans"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "What has happened in terms of your legal actions with both BP and Transocean who controlled the rig?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Transocean has filed a lawsuit against me and my children, forcing us to go to the lawyers in New Orleans and be apart of the multidistrict litigation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["BP", "Transocean"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Did you say that Transocean is suing you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes, sir, they filed a lawsuit against me and my children and the rest of the people that were killed to limit their liability, to limit what they're responsible for.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transocean"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transocean"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Why on earth would Transocean be able to file any kind of lawsuit against widows like Shelley in this position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Piers, Transocean picked up on a 150-year-old outdated technicality in the law where they could file a limitation proceeding, saying we're going to take you widows and you victims, you hurt people, to a court of our choosing and limit you, your recovery, to the value of our rig at the time that it sunk.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transocean"], "PERSON": ["Shelley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transocean"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Steve Newman"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Why do you think they're just not prepared to settle and look after you all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, you know, Mr. Steve Newman, the CEO of Transocean, sat in my living room and told me not to worry, that we would be taken care of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "To bring things to a conclusion that you feel is fair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "At this point, I'm just excited that he's willing to listen to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transocean", "BP"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "CC", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "DT", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Courtney, did you want to say something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "I was just going to add that I'm hoping that we can come to an agreement that both parties will be OK with and because, you know, Transocean and BP both have -- their public relations department has been just terrible, if you ask me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["BP"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, you'll have to ask BP what they said and why they said it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Why have these widows not have their money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "They just filed with me in the last few weeks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Why can't you just take a slug of that cash and give it to them and say, you know something, this is deserving for you to be able to rebuild your lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "I have every intention of doing that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "How many claims have you so far denied?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Aren't they the very people that you ought to be helping, not basically throwing to the wolves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "I agree with you again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transocean"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "How do you feel -- how do you feel about Transocean awarding executives bonuses after this incident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "You know, that's not -- I've got enough problems of my own without worrying about Transocean.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transocean"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Can you offer them any kind of comfort the other way, that there isn't going to be another explosion and more problems to their livelihoods?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Piers, I can't do more than what I can do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "And they are crying out for cash, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "They are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Was that the most sensible thing to do in the middle of all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Let me tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "And isn't there a kind of moral compulsion on your part to look at this in a fairer way and say, OK, you know, we clearly see that the pattern of trading amongst many of these fishermen, who were making very little sums of fun, but were wiped out by this, doesn't involve the paper trail that we would need normally, but we are going to override that and just give them some help anyway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Why don't you try putting the heart before the head on this one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "EINBERG: I'll listen to what you have to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Are many being denied money they should be getting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "VBG", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "You know, we continue to the see what we think are significant problems in the claims process.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Yes, those are just part of disaster rhetoric.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Philippe, how bad an environmental disaster was this, now that we have had time to properly assess it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, Piers, the extent of the environmental damage is now just becoming apparent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "What is your gut feeling about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, Piers, I think the future is unknown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110419pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "How many people do you think are not getting the money they ought to get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Every single person who doesn't get made whole from this is too many.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]